canadasmotorcycle.ca 2015-03-22

# Privacy Policy - Canada's Motorcycle

### INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE

Canada's Motorcycle is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement.

### ORDER

We request information from the user on our order form. Here a user must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer's orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user.

### COOKIES

A cookie is a piece of information that a Web site transfers to an individual's hard drive for record keeping purposes. Cookies make Web-surfing easier for you by saving your passwords, purchases, and preferences while you're at our site. The use of cookies is an Industry standard, and you'll find cookies at most major websites.

### LOG FILES

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

### SHARING

We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. We use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. 

These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.

### LINKS

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.

### NEWSLETTER

If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and e-mail address. You may opt-out of our newsletter at any moment by clicking the un-subscribe button at the bottom of our newsletter emails.
